search.gov.hk 2009-03-01

# GovHK: Privacy Policy

The Government of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region ("the Government") is concerned to ensure that all personal data submitted through GovHK are handled in accordance with the relevant provisions of the [Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance](http://www.pcpd.org.hk/english/ordinance/ordfull.html "Personal Data
\(Privacy\) Ordinance") ( http://www.pcpd.org.hk/english/ordinance/ordfull.html ).

The Government will record visits to GovHK without collecting any personal identifiable information of users. Such general statistics are collected for the compilation of statistical reports and the diagnosis of problems with or concerning computer systems to help the Government improve GovHK.

For different purposes and at different times you may be invited to provide personal data to the Government through GovHK on a voluntary basis. Personal information may include name, telephone number, mailing address or e-mail address. The Government will specify the collection purpose and intended usage of your data when it invites you to provide such information and advise you how you may request access to or correction of the personal data provided.

Unless permitted or required by law, the Government will not disclose your personal data to any third parties without your prior consent.

GovHK uses SSL protocol to encrypt data during network transmission to protect your personal data. All personal data you provide to the Government via GovHK are secured, and access to them is restricted to authorised personnel only.

Search service on GovHK is provided by Yahoo! Hong Kong Limited ("Yahoo!"). We are advised by Yahoo! that it does not collect personal identifiable information while serving search results through GovHK. Yahoo! will share the anonymous data it collects through the search service with the Government for compiling traffic analysis on government websites. The Government will not match the data obtained from any such search activity with any personal data possibly held by the Government.

This Privacy Policy has been translated into Chinese. If there is any inconsistency or ambiguity between the English version and the Chinese version, the English version shall prevail.

January 2007
